(upbeat music)
♪ I'll always think of you ♪
♪ Inside of my private thoughts ♪
♪ I can imagine you ♪
♪ Touching my private parts ♪
♪ And just the thought of you ♪
♪ I can't help but touch myself ♪
♪ That's why I want you so bad ♪
♪ Just one night of ♪
♪ Moonlight, with you there beside me ♪
♪ All night, doin' it again and again ♪
♪ You know, I want you so bad ♪
♪ Baby, baby, baby, baby ♪
♪ Ohh, I get so high ♪
♪ When I'm around you, baby ♪
♪ I can touch the sky ♪
♪ You make my temperature rise ♪
♪ Baby, you're makin' me high ♪
♪ Baby, baby, baby, baby ♪
♪ Can't get my mind off you ♪
♪ I think I might be obsessed ♪
♪ The very thought of you ♪
♪ Makes me want to get undressed ♪
♪ I wanna be with you ♪
♪ Inspite of what my heart says ♪
♪ I guess I want you too bad ♪
♪ All I want is ♪
♪ Moonlights, with you there inside me ♪
♪ All night, doin' it again and again ♪
♪ You know, I want you so bad ♪
♪ Baby, baby, baby, baby ♪
♪ Ohh, I get so high ♪
♪ When I'm around you, baby ♪
♪ I can touch the sky ♪
♪ You make my temperature rise ♪
♪ Boy, you're makin' me high ♪
♪ Baby, baby, baby, baby ♪
♪ I want to feel your heart
and soul inside of me ♪
♪ Let's make a deal you roll, I lick ♪
♪ And we can go flying into ecstasy ♪
♪ Oh, darlin' you and me ♪
♪ Light my fire, blow my flame ♪
♪ Take me, take me, take me away ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Well all I only want is ♪
♪ Moonlights, with you there inside me ♪
♪ All night, doin' it again and again ♪
♪ Baby, I want you so bad ♪
♪ Baby, baby, baby, baby ♪
♪ I get so high ♪
♪ When I'm around you, baby ♪
♪ I can touch the sky ♪
♪ You make my temperature rise ♪
♪ You're makin' me high ♪
♪ Baby, baby, baby, baby ♪
♪ I get so high ♪